{
	"rounds": [
		{
			"categories": [
				{
					"name": "Musical Mayhem",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "Mamma Mia is a jukebox musical based on the music of what band?",
							"answer": "ABBA",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "This girl group from the show Grease shares its name with a type of apple",
							"answer": "Pink Ladies",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "Who composed the hit musical Cats?",
							"answer": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "What is the longest-running musical on Broadway?",
							"answer": "The Phantom of the Opera",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What original musical song is the most-streamed on Spotify?",
							"answer": "Defying Gravity",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Caped Crusaders",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "What is Batman's real name?",
							"answer": "Bruce Wayne",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "In what year was the Iron Man film first released?",
							"answer": "2008",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "In the movie Avengers: Endgame, what video game did Thor play?",
							"answer": "Fortnite",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "In Iron Man 2, what fake name does Natasha Romanov use?",
							"answer": "Natalie Rushman",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What is Pepper Potts allergic to?",
							"answer": "Strawberries",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Matrimonial Moments",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "What is the biggest wedding destination in the USA?",
							"answer": "Las Vegas",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "What is the name of the cup traditionally drank from at Scottish weddings?",
							"answer": "Quaich",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "Who started the white wedding dress trend?",
							"answer": "Queen Victoria",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "Why does the woman traditionally stand on the left side?",
							"answer": "So that the groom's sword arm is free",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What is the most expensive wedding dress ever sold?",
							"answer": "Â£8.2 million",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "The Journey Begins",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "When was our first kiss?",
							"answer": "4th January 2019",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "Where was our first date?",
							"answer": "ðŸ‘Œ Cheeky Nandos ðŸ‘Œ",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "What was the first TV show we watched together?",
							"answer": "Sex Education",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "At whose birthday celebration did Max ask Isla to be his girlfriend?",
							"answer": "Catherine",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What date did Isla meet Max's friends for the first time?",
							"answer": "16th January 2019",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Who's in the Shadows?",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "img:max-sil",
							"answer": "img:max",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "img:ali-sil",
							"answer": "img:ali",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "img:becky-sil",
							"answer": "img:becky",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "img:isla-sil",
							"answer": "img:isla",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "img:group-sil",
							"answer": "img:group",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"categories": [
				{
					"name": "Our Big Day",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "What is the name of our wedding venue?",
							"answer": "Falside Mill",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "What time does the ceremony start?",
							"answer": "2pm",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "What is the welcome drink at our wedding?",
							"answer": "Mango Bellini",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "What is the name of the tartan Max is wearing at the wedding?",
							"answer": "Flower of Scotland",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What feature of our wedding shares its name with a restaurant that recently closed its Glasgow branch?",
							"answer": "Tuk Tuk",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "The Man Behind the Groom",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "What musical instrument does Max play?",
							"answer": "Violin",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "What condition does Max have?",
							"answer": "Scoliosis",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "At what age did Max meet Isla?",
							"answer": "20",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "What is the name of the high school Max attended?",
							"answer": "Balwearie High School",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What was the name of Max's childhood pet, and what animal were they?",
							"answer": "Timmy the Cat",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Isla Unveiled",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "Who is Isla's favorite singer?",
							"answer": "Taylor Swift",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "How old was Isla when she met Max?",
							"answer": "18",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "What elective did Isla fail in her first year?",
							"answer": "French",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "What is the only concert Isla has been to?",
							"answer": "One Direction",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "How many Sims packs does Isla own?",
							"answer": "37",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "The Whiskered Wonder",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "What type of cat is Louie?",
							"answer": "Tuxedo",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "How old is Louie?",
							"answer": "2",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "What health condition does Louie have that requires him to take daily medication?",
							"answer": "Stress-Related Cystitis (Anxiety)",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "What zodiac sign is Louie?",
							"answer": "Leo",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "What was the name of Louie's mother?",
							"answer": "Nala",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "The Groomsmaids",
					"questions": [
						{
							"points": 100,
							"question": "Who among us is the eldest?",
							"answer": "Alistair",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 200,
							"question": "What were the names of the two escape rooms from last year?",
							"answer": "The Black Pearl and Gold Rush",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 300,
							"question": "How many of the you, to Isla and Max's knowledge, have tattoos?",
							"answer": "2",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 400,
							"question": "Which of you RSVP'd first to Isla and Max's wedding invitation?",
							"answer": "Ross",
							"done": false
						},
						{
							"points": 500,
							"question": "Who was the first person that Isla met during her initial introduction to Max's circle of friends?",
							"answer": "Jenny",
							"done": false
						}
					]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}